<content>
	<dom>
		<jum-title>Senior Backend &amp; Frontend Developer</jum-title>
		
		<jum-description-1>I'm a passionate programmer with the unreachable quest to achieve the perfect code. I've participated in many developing projects, from websites to advanced web applications.</jum-description-1>
		<jum-description-2>Studied in La Salle University the Cybernetics Engineering </jum-description-2>
		<jum-desc-help-2> - 2006-2011 promotion</jum-desc-help-2>
		<jum-description-2-1> in Chihuahua, Chih. Mexico. However, my specialty is the Web Programming, I started building websites back in 2008, with professional experience since 2010.</jum-description-2-1>

		<jum-description-3>I'm cofounder of</jum-description-3>
		<jum-desc-help-3>uVicate</jum-desc-help-3>
		<jum-description-3-1> a company dedicated to the Internet software development, playing the role of director in the development area.</jum-description-3-1>

		<technical_knowledge>Technical knowledge</technical_knowledge>

		<kn-title-1>Database design</kn-title-1>
		<kn-sub-1> With MySQL, SQLite.</kn-sub-1>
		<kb-main-1>From with the entity-relationship model, design the relational model, writing the sintax code for creating it, satisfying the normalization rules of course. To making queries, stored functions, etc. And advanced SQL code.</kb-main-1>

		<kn-title-2>Serverside programming </kn-title-2>
		<kn-sub-2>using PHP</kn-sub-2>
		<kb-main-2>I have experience with object oriented programming in this language. I've realized a great amount of libraries and APIs in different projects and systems.</kb-main-2>

		<kn-title-3>Clientside programming </kn-title-3>
		<kn-sub-3>using JavaScript, HTML and CSS</kn-sub-3>
		<kn-main-3>Using newest design patterns and "Prototype-Programming" giving the maximum performance in the application. Also having experience with HTML5 technologies like IndexedDB and Web Sockets. Integration with 3rd parties like Google, Dropbox, Facebook, etc.</kn-main-3>

		<kn-title-4>Elegant codes</kn-title-4>
		<kn-sub-4> and open</kn-sub-4>
		<kn-main-4>The code must be easy to read, maintain and expand. I've developed some APIs that are used by different developers around the world, Check out my open source repositories in</kn-main-4>
		<kn-main-4-1>Github</kn-main-4-1>
		<kn-main-4-2>! If you're a programmer like me, I'd like to know your work to.</kn-main-4-2>

		<kn-title-5>My not so specialty </kn-title-5>
		<kn-sub-5>Python programming</kn-sub-5>
		<kn-main-5>In 2012 I wrote a hybrid code in Python and Web technologies. For Linux, specifically for the Ubuntu distribution. Although I never published it, inspired me for realizing the "WebApp" API and my "ExpMan" project.</kn-main-5>

		<contact-me>Contact me</contact-me>
		<contact-phone>Phone</contact-phone>
		<contact-email>Email</contact-email>
		<about-social>Social networks</about-social>
		<about-location>Location</about-location>

		<curiosities>Fun Facts</curiosities>
		<f-1>8 Hours programming</f-1>
		<fm-1>Daily</fm-1>

		<f-2>+10,000 Code lines</f-2>
		<fm-2>Monthly</fm-2>

		<f-3>2 Hours reading</f-3>
		<fm-3>Per day</fm-3>

		<f-4>10 cups of coffe</f-4>
		<fm-4>Per week</fm-4>

		<f-5>6 Playing RO (And now LOL)</f-5>
		<fm-5>Per weekend</fm-5>
	</dom>
</content>